<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<section id="2691">
  <number>0</number>
  <name></name>
  <summary>&lt;p style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Welcome to Motivating Adult Learners to Persist!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;img src="@@PLUGINFILE@@/MicrosoftTeams-image%20%2810%29.png" alt="" width="400" height="267" role="presentation" class="img-responsive atto_image_button_right"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This course and the accompanying materials were developed by Kristi Reyes in collaboration with the American Institutes for Research.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This course supports teachers' understanding of eleven strategies that motivate adult learners to persist, especially those described in the National Research Council's Improving Adult Literacy Instruction: Supporting Learning and Motivation. It also provides teachers with guidance to make focused observations of how these strategies are implemented. Many adult learners face considerable barriers to their academic success and often have many competing responsibilities (family, work, etc.) Only by persisting in school are these learners able to set and meet academic goals and improve their learning outcomes. To help motivate students to continue learning and make progress, adult education instructors need specific knowledge and skills in delivering evidence-based instruction that will support their learners to persist. Beginning teachers can gain competence in these areas by working through a teacher induction program with a mentor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Course Length and Format&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This course will take about 3 hours and 30 minutes to complete.&amp;nbsp;Please note that items with solid boxes can be self-checked to indicate completion; however, the self-assessment and all learning checks are graded and required for completion.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This course is intended for multiple audiences:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;adult education and English language acquisition instructors,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;program administrators and coordinators; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;professional development trainers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can enhance your learning in this course by doing the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gain new knowledge and skills through readings, scenarios, videos, and reflections.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download this handout, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://lincs.ed.gov/sites/default/files/2023-02/LINCS-SlfrflctnActyWrkbk-MALP-508.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Self-Reflection and Activity Workbook for Motivating Adult Learners to Persist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span class="nolink"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;in order to jot down your ideas—for your eyes only.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earn a certificate of completion by viewing all activities in the course (unless marked "optional").&amp;nbsp;Please note that the checkmark for some items may not appear as "viewed" until after this course page is refreshed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Course Objectives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upon successful completion of this online course, participants will be able to do the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify strategies that motivate adult learners to persist and describe examples of their application;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Observe an adult education class and describe how these strategies are being implemented; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select three course resources to support your implementation of motivation and persistence strategies in your practice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This course was
originally developed under contract with&amp;nbsp;the American Institutes for
Research (AIR)&amp;nbsp;with funding from the U.S. Department of Education (ED),
Office of Career, Technical, and Adult Education (OCTAE), under Contract
No.&amp;nbsp;ED-CFO-10-A-0066. This course has been updated under contract
with&amp;nbsp;AIR&amp;nbsp;with funding from the ED, OCTAE, under Contract No.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;i&gt;91990020A-0014/ 91990022F-0346. &lt;em&gt;The&amp;nbsp;content
and&amp;nbsp;opinions expressed herein do not necessarily represent the positions
or policies of the U.S. Department of Education, and no official endorsement by
the U.S. Department of Education should be inferred.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;The course may
contain resources by a third party outside of the Department of Education. As
such, the Department is not responsible for its content, nor can it guarantee
it is accessible in accordance with Section 508 of the Rehabilitation Act of
1973. If you need access to an accessible version, please reach out to the
third-party vendor for assistance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="color: #000000;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: arial,helvetica,sans-serif;"&gt;To get started, click on each unit's title below and access its contents and activities, beginning with "Course Introduction."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</summary>
  <summaryformat>1</summaryformat>
  <sequence></sequence>
  <visible>1</visible>
  <availabilityjson>{"op":"&amp;","c":[],"showc":[]}</availabilityjson>
  <timemodified>1680203743</timemodified>
</section>